<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Mostly Harmless</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Mostly Harmless</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 14:38:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Go on Azure</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/go-on-azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 14:38:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/go-on-azure/</guid>
      <description>The Go programming language is a fun application for building system tools and it really shines in the cloud space. Many well known cloud projects are built using it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Go</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/learning-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/learning-go/</guid>
      <description>For 2024 I will be learning Go. Well, relearning some of it as I have coded small systems applications in Go before. I will be posting any links and tools I discover here on this blog with the tag of golang. The book I will be using is not that new but, it not costly. I it is The Go Programming Language, by Alan A. A. Donovan and Brian W. Kernighan It is from 2016 so will be missing some of the newer features of Go such as Genetics and Modules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loki and the Logs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/loki-and-the-logs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/loki-and-the-logs/</guid>
      <description>Loki is a log management system. What another one, why yes, but let me explain the idea behind this one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infrastructure as Code</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-the-duck-is-ioc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-the-duck-is-ioc/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post in a series that aims to introduce infrastructure as code. We will start in the post with a discussion of why you would want to use IoC and then the different types, before giving some examples of IoC in action.&#xA;What is IoC # Simply IoC is a way of describing your infrastructure in code. In the same what if you were to build a building or a ship you would first design the system using plans.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
